statelife.net 2014-11-20

# Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business

### We, Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business., are committed to protecting any data that we collect concerning you. By using our services you agree to the use of the data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We, additionally, are firmly committed to the principles of the EU-US and US-Swiss Safe Harbor program setup by United States Department of Commerce, the European Union (.EU.), and Switzerland. Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business's Safe Harbor Certification can be found here [Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business/safehrbr/list.aspx](http://export.gov/safeHarbor/) More information about Safe Harbor principles can be found here [http://www.export.gov/safeHarbor/](http://export.gov/safeHarbor/)

## We are committed to protecting your privacy

We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. This Policy indicates the type of processes that may result in data being collected about you. The purpose of this Privacy Policy to enable you to understand which personal identifying information ("PII", "Personal Information") of yours is collected, how and when we might use your information, who has access to this information, and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our website.  

> #### We may collect the following information:

> \- name or user-name
> 
> \- contact information including email address   
> 
> 
> \- demographic information such as geo-locations, preferences and interests other information relevant to customer investment and/or offers. 

> #### What we do with the information we gather

> We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: Internal record keeping, services reviews authentication and verification . We may use the information to improve our project and services. We may periodically send promotional emails about new special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, (phone, fax or mail when availble). We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. 

> #### Security

> We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure,we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

> #### How we use cookies

> A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

> #### Controlling your personal information

> You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information by not filling any forms on this website. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by contacting us using contact us form at the bottom of the site pages with the request to modify or delete your personal information previously  submitted to Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business.

> #### How to Unsubscribe from our list

> If You no longer wish to receive communications from Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business, it’s very easy to stop. Simply scroll down to the bottom of any email and click the “unsubscribe” link. Every email that is sent from Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business mailing list is specially coded with a link that is tied to your email subscription account. If you no longer wish to receive emails from Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business, simply scroll to the bottom of the email and click the unsubscribe link. 

> #### Details of Personal Information

> We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please send us a message using contact us form at the bottom of the site pages. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

## Information Collected

We may collect any or all of the information that via both automated means such as communications profiles and cookies. Personal Information you give us depends on the type of service or support inqury, and may include your name, address, telephone number and email address, dates of birth, types of service plan, payment history, manner of payment, amount of payments, date of payments, or other payment information. The financial information will be transferred only be used for the Plans Life and services you purchased. 

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our site and servers, track access, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. It is possible that personal information about a customer may be included in the log files due to the normal functions of IP addresses and Web browsing.

## Cookies

Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small text files - "cookies" - that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account. We use cookies to save your preferences and login information, and provide personalized functionality. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but be aware that this will disable some of the functionality on the Statelife.net | We Do Straight Business's website.

## Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about Users upon valid request by government or law officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect your property and rights, or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or stop activity we consider illegal or unethical.

## Changes to this Policy

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, or if you want to know what information we have collected about you, please email us at [privacy@statelife.net](mailto:privacy@statelife.net) You can also correct any factual errors in that information or require us to remove your details from any list under our control. You can also email us at [privacy@statelife.net](mailto:privacy@statelife.net)
